(Leonard:)...are you embarrassed
to have me around your friends?
(Penny:)Oh, my God, no.
Why would you ask that?
(Leonard:)Well, you know, I just noticed
I haven't really met any of them.
(Penny:)-Sure you have.
-Well, yeah, no.
(Leonard:)I met the huge ex-boyfriend...
...and the smaller-yet-still-larger-than-me
ex-boyfriend.
By the way, were they here today?
(Penny:)-Of course not.
-Why would they? Why would I ask?
(Leonard:)Why am I rambling?
Why don't you stop me?
Leonard, look, if you wanna meet
my friends, that would be great.
(Penny:)I just-- You know,
I didn't want you to be bored.
(Leonard:)I wouldn't be bored.
Why would I be bored?
Well, because they're not
genius scientists.
(Leonard:)Penny, I like all sorts of people.
(Leonard:)In fact, some of my best friends
aren't geniuses.
(Penny:)Like who?
(Leonard:)Okay, some of my Facebook friends
aren't geniuses.
But-- My point is,
if we're gonna be a couple...
(Leonard:)-...I should be friends with your friends.
-Okay, great.